Cody F. Ktestakis

CodyKtestakis@yahoo.com (801) 580-8581 124 2nd Ave New York, New York 10003

PROFILE

A skilled Quality Assurance Analyst and Inspector with over 3 years of experience at Edwards Lifesciences and currently working two years at BioFire Diagnostics. A highly effective communicator with the ability to develop and execute QA test plans. Consistently trusted to lead and develop test strategies for high-visibility, highly complex product and application development scenarios.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Certified in LEAN
- Manual QA Analysis
- Project Management
- Microsoft Office
- JIRA

- HTML & CSS
- Basic Javascript
- BlueHill
- Test Case Management

EXPERIENCE

BIOFIRE DIAGNOSTICS QUALITY TECHNICIAN III

Apr. 2018-Present

- Work closely with management teams to ensure calibration are up-to-date on instruments/tools
- Review documents for errors to limit risk during auditing by FDA
- Audit technician stations. Ensure paperwork is signed in real time and all items are calibrated
- Verifying calibrations dates on all tools (Multi-Meter, Temp-Meter, Torque Drivers) and software systems (ArC-Lite Version)
- NCRs (Non Conformance Report) move nonconforming product in quarantine and investigate the failure of the product

BIOFIRE DIAGNOSTICS QUALITY TECHNICIAN I

Oct. 2016-Apr. 2018

- Performed visual inspection on FilmArray Instrument looking for loose wiring and screws in instrument
- Reviewed documentations before scanning it into the DHRs (Device History Records)
- Assessed requirements and analyzed documentation
- Created and documented test cases
- Worked on audit procedures, ensured every machine collaboration is up to date, verified expiration dates and confirmed it was up to regulatory requirement

EDWARDS LIFE SCIENCE QUALITY ASSURANCE

Jun. 2014- Oct. 2016

- Worked closely with engineers to find requirements and provide solutions for stakeholders into completing a good work flow
- Worked in a PV Lab testing samples, measuring samples with caliber, smart scope and mechanical data
- · Performed manual, exploratory testing. Completed visual inspection on frames and verified labels
- Use BlueHill software on Instron test samples to create graph measurements
- Mixed chemicals to complete test samples and working under a microscope

EDWARDS LIFE SCIENCE, MATERIAL HANDLER

May. 2013-Jun. 2014

- Cycle counted and ordered parts for the lines
- Communicated with buyer planners on adding more inventory to the warehouse

EDWARDS LIFE SCIENCE, MANUFACTURING OPERATOR

Jan. 2013-May. 2013

- Issued out inventory for work orders, boxed units, stacked pallets and worked with JDE
- Documentation clerk, went over paper work inventory counts and ensured quantity matches what is being scrapped on the work order

EDUCATION

Salt Lake Community College, Salt Lake City, UT

Aug. 2018

Courses: Intro to quality Systems & Basic Manufacturing Skills

Southpointe High School, Salt Lake City, UT

June 2018